const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "4.6",
    title: "Modal verbs - must/have to, don't have to",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "Muszę iść.",
    back: "I have to go./ I must go.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy musisz iść?",
    back: "Do you have to go?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie muszę iść.",
    back: "I don't have to go."
  },
  {
    front: "Musisz wstać.",
    back: "You have to get up./ You must get up.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy musisz wstać?",
    back: "Do you have to get up?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie musisz wstawać. Jest wcześnie.",
    back: "You don't have to get up. It's early.",
  },
  {
    front: "On musi zarezerwować lot.",
    back: "He has to book the flight./ He must book the flight.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy on musi zarezerwować lot?",
    back: "Does he have to book the flight?",
  },
  {
    front: "On nie musi rezerwować lotu. Jedzie pociągiem.",
    back: "He doesn't have to book the flight. He's going by train.",
  },
  {
    front: "Ona musi się dużo uczyć.",
    back: "She has to study hard./ She must study hard.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy ona musi się dużo uczyć?",
    back: "Does she have to study hard?",
  },
  {
    front: "Ona nie musi się uczyć. Zdała egzamin!",
    back: "She doesn't have to study. She passed the exam!",
  },
  {
    front: "To musi się skończyć.",
    back: "It has to end./ It must end.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy to musi się skończyć?",
    back: "Does it have to end?",
  },
  {
    front: "To nie musi się kończyć.",
    back: "It doesn't have to end.",
  },
  {
    front: "Musimy płacić czynsz.",
    back: "We have to pay the rent./ We must pay the rent.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy musimy płacić czynsz?",
    back: "Do we have to pay the rent?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie musimy płacić czynszu. Mieszkamy z rodzicami.",
    back: "We don't have to pay the rent. We live with our parents.",
  },
  {
    front: "Musisz posprzątać swój pokój.",
    back: "You have to clean up your room./ You must clean up your room.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy musisz sprzątać swój pokój?",
    back: "Do you have to clean up your room?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie musisz sprzątać swojego pokoju. Wygląda idealnie!",
    back: "You don't have to clean up your room. It looks perfect!",
  },
  {
    front: "Muszą wyprowadzić psa na spacer.",
    back: "They have to take the dog for a walk./ They must take the dog for a walk.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy oni muszą wyprowadzać psa na spacer?",
    back: "Do they have to take the dog for a walk?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie muszą wyprowadzać psa na spacer. Mają kota.",
    back: "They don't have to take the dog for a walk. They have a cat.",
  },
  {
    front: "Muszę to zrobić.",
    back: "I have to do it./ I have got to do it./ I've gotta do it.",
  },
  {
    front: "Musisz iść.",
    back: "You have to go./ You have got to go./ You've gotta go.",
  },
  {
    front: "On musi pracować.",
    back: "He has to work./ He has got to work./ He's gotta go.",
  },
  {
    front: "Ona musi to sprzedać.",
    back: "She has to sell it./ She has got to sell it./ She's gotta sell it.",
  },
  {
    front: "Musimy pomyśleć.",
    back: "We have to think./ We have got to think./ We've gotta think.",
  },
  {
    front: "Muszą się uczyć.",
    back: "They have to study./ They have got to study./ They've gotta study.",
  },
];
export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
